arab.de 2002-12-08

# Privacy Statement - Arab German Consulting

**Arab German Consulting** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [**Arab German Consulting**](http://www.arab.de/) **Information Automatically Logged** We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your preferences. 

**Arab German Consulting** does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. We ensure you that all information provided will be held in the strictest of confidence. 

**Cookies** Our Site uses cookies and other technics to deliver content specific to your interests, to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site's **Terms Of Use** or to protect our services and our visitors against unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail", "spam", "chain letters", "pyramid schemes", or any other form of solicitation. **Registration Forms** Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email and country). Contact information from the registration forms is used to inform our visitors about new updates, information about our company. The visitor's contact information is also used to get in touch with other visitors when necessary. See [**Trade Board 2001**](http://www.arab.de/etrade/trade1.html) and [**International Business Opportunities.**](http://www.arab.de/cgi-bin/ebizop.cgi) **External Links** This site contains links to other sites. **Arab German Consulting** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. **Public Forums** This site makes forums, message boards available to its users [**Trade Board 2001**](http://www.arab.de/etrade/trade1.html) and [**International Business Opportunities.**](http://www.arab.de/cgi-bin/ebizop.cgi) Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **Security** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. **Contacting Arab German Consulting** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please do not hesitate to contact us: **[info@arab.de](mailto:webmaster@arab.de)**
